<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SimpleTourGuide</string>



    <string name="category_start">Start</string>
    <string name="category_northtour">North Tour</string>
    <string name="category_southtour">South Tour</string>
    <string name="category_easttour">East Tour</string>


    <string name="districts_title_1">Sady</string>
    <string name="districts_title_2">Zoliborskie</string>
    <string name="districts_title_3">Dzielnica</string>

    <string name="east_title_1">Daschund</string>
    <string name="east_title_2">Grochow</string>
    <string name="east_title_3">Kinowa</string>

    <string name="north_title_1">Rotunda</string>
    <string name="north_title_2">Rotunda</string>
    <string name="north_title_3">Stadion</string>

    <string name="south_title_1">Crossroads</string>
    <string name="south_title_2">National Library</string>
    <string name="south_title_3">X</string>


    <string name="districts_1">Built in 70s, Ursynow\\’s design was created with a keynote - “for serving people”. Individual parts of district were formed from small colonies of short and tall buildings, creating their internal courtyards with squares and greenery. Each building had to be a little different, because the diversity was meant be the distinguishing characteristic of every residential.\n" +
                "After the construction the lack of shops, pharmacies, clinics and communication was based on the assumption of the imminent launch of subway (for which the Varsovians had to wait till late 90’)). Residents praise the apartments mostly for their layout, but ask them about  driving a nail through a concrete slab and sit comfortable - prepare for an anger-management-therapy material..\n"</string>
    <string name="districts_2">Nowadays Ursynow aspires to be an intellectual block - every third inhabitant has an university degree. Well connected with the center of Warsaw, it is a frequent place to look for a flat. Rental or sales offers tend to disappear in a few days!</string>
    <string name="districts_3">Cwil’s Hill - artificially created hill during the construction of a housing estate. 18 meters high with 3 vertices. Named after one of the engineers working on the construction site. Beautiful skyline of Ursynow Polnocny and Sluzew included.</string>

    <string name="east_1">The numbers are impressive: 508 meters long, 43 staircases, 1200 inhabitants, 10 flats per each staircase and two flats per one floor. In the back, 132 almost-underground garages. In the collective consciousness of Varsovians it is not only the longest block in the capital, but probably in the whole world - and visually it certainly is. Close neighbour f of  the East Warsaw Railway Station, welcomes travelers with its monumentality. Why is this monolith standing here? For purely practical reasons as Jaroslaw Trybus, deputy director of the Warsaw Museum said: \"The building was built to cover the view of the old, crumbling buildings on Szmulki. It was meant to serve as a big screen covering what was uncomfortable </string>
    <string name="east_2">The longest facility in Warsaw with a hard to comprehend number of 2,330 flats with 5,000 habitants. The complex  consisting of interconnected 23 blocks  covering the area of 11 hectares with total length of 1.5 km was designed by Zofia and Oskar Hansen and founded in 1970. Staircases, corridors and galleries were supposed to give the impression of “space penetrating the buildings”. That is probably the case, especially for someone who gets lost in this maze of walls.</string>
    <string name="east_3">Asymmetrical, square balconies create a dynamic pattern with penetrating forms of chiaroscuro falling from each side. Designed by Bohdan Lewandowski and Maciej Szawerenowski, realized 1960-66.</string>


    <string name="north_1">In the past times ironically called the \"generals hat\", today is  one of the favorite meeting places is located at the intersection of the two most important thoroughfares of the city - Jerozolimskie Avenue and Marszalkowska Street. The true pearl of modernism, decorated with a characteristic roof, slightly inclined towards north-east is a part of the Eastern Wall urban complex.\n" + "In 1979 took place the most tragic accident of post-war Poland. Gas explosion which took place there in 1979 is considered on of the most trafic accidents of post-war Poland. The explosion taking place during rush hours took lives of 49 people. Rotunda was rebuilt after the explosion, however the abandonment of the signature transparent glasses caused loosing a lot from its past charm. The current reconstruction of the modernism wonder brings hope for restoring the assumptions of the original project.</string>
    <string name="north_2">\nCreated during 1960-1966 based on the design of Zbigniew Karpinski.</string>
    <string name="north_3">The stadium at Marymont is a pearl of structural modernism. Designed by the eminent Polish architect Stanislaw Barylski and built in the 1950s. Stadium creates a sense of intimacy with its gentle, harmonious details. Arched passages made of solid concrete serve as a beautiful complement to the entire facility. This theater was a host and witness of the famous sports stories  with Kazimierz Gorski beginning his coaching career and Zinedine Zidane playing one of his first matches in the French national team among others. Despite its poor condition, stadium is still alive with many minor sport clubs and associations. Recently social actions were risen aimed for restoring the stadium - without results for now.</string>

    <string name="south_1">It is a "crossroads square" and not without reason. A multi-level interchange node located next to the Chancellery of the Prime Minister, Lazienki Park and many embassies. When you take a look around, you can not spot  any closure of the square. Only on one side we have the opportunity to see modernist, concave blocks. They appear to open some kind of a gate to the North Middletown. It is worth taking a rest near a lonely fountain in the middle of the roundabout itself. Use underground passages - they are decorated with tiles from the 60s and filled with a small art galleries.</string>
    <string name="south_2">The written history of National Library building could accommodate a small library by itself. The winning project was announced in 1963, although the construction was completed over thirteen years later. In recent years it was heavily involved in numerous renovations and digitization of its resources.</string>
    <string name="south_3">The blocks built in 1971-1973 are a great example of how to delineate thought-out lines of perspectives using balconies. The characteristic curvature of the buildings laid out on the X pattern generates a lot of curvatures of falling chiaroscuro.\n" + "Project: Jan Zdanowicz</string>

</resources>
